(Leonard:)All right, well, anyway, Darwin
observed that when two groups
(Leonard:)of finches competed
over the same food source,
(Leonard:)eventually one of them would
evolve a different beak shape
(Leonard:)so they could feed on
something else.
(Priya:)Okay.
(Leonard:)So what do you think we can
learn from that behavior
(Leonard:)that we can apply
to our own lives?
(Penny:)Uh, a bird in the hand is worth
two in the bush?
(Leonard:)Sure, that has birds in it.
(Penny:)It's fun talking to you,
Leonard; I always learn stuff.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna count that.
PRIYA: Do you really have
to wear that in bed?
(Leonard:)Yeah. The doctor didn't want me
to rub my eye during the night.
(Leonard:)It was either this or one
of those giant neck cones.